pdf-format.com 2017-05-25

# PDF Reader & Writer: view, create, modify, print PDF files

## Privacy Policy

### Changes to this Policy

This Privacy Policy may occasionally change. Any Policy changes will be posted on this page. Each version of this policy will be denoted at the top of this page by its effective date.

### Privacy Policy

We, at Interactive Brands, respect your right to privacy and we are committed to protecting it.

This statement discloses the information that we gather and track, how we use the information, and with whom we share this same information.

### Personal Information

You can visit any of our Web sites without indicating who you are, and without revealing any personal information about yourself. If you choose to buy from this Web site, we ask you to provide basic information such as your First Name, Last Name and e­mail address. This will be used to set up your private account, your invoice, and to send your purchase confirmation. Your personal information will NEVER BE DISCLOSED OR SHARED WITH ANY THIRD PARTY without your explicit consent.

Transaction information such as credit card details, billing addresses and/or phone numbers are required to purchase and activate your membership. If you provide us with personal information or credit information about somebody else, such as a family member, friend or associate, we will assume that you have their permission to do so.

### Communication Preferences (how to opt-out)

If you do not wish to receive marketing communications from us or participate in our customization program, simply choose to opt-out by Clicking on the link to unsubscribe in any of the received emails; you will be automatically opted out of our mailing list.

### Fulfilling your Transaction Request

To fulfill your requests (i.e. access to customer´s area, technical support, etc.), you must allow us to use your personal information to identify you as a client.

### Information Security

We intend to protect your personal information and maintain its integrity. To help us do this, we have implemented appropriate measures and processes, such as SSL encryption when transmitting sensitive information.

### Cookies and Other Web Technologies

To help us provide better customer service, we sometimes collect non­identifiable information from visits to our Web sites. For example, we may keep track of the domains from which people visit, and we may also measure visitor activity. We may use this data to analyze trends and statistics and to help us provide better customer service.

We collect the aforementioned information through the use of various technologies, including so­called "cookies". A cookie is a piece of data that a Web site can send to your browser, which may then be stored on your computer as an anonymous tag that identifies your computer without disclosing your personal information. Some of our pages use cookies, and other technologies to better serve you when you return to the Web site. You can set your browser to notify you before you receive a cookie, allowing you the chance to decide whether or not to accept it. You can also set your browser to turn off cookies. If you do so, however, some Web sites may not work properly.

### Security, Intrusion, and Detection

For Web site security purposes, and to ensure that our Web site remains available to all visitors, all network traffic is monitored in order to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, cause damage, or conduct criminal activity. To protect the system from unauthorized use and to ensure that the system is functioning properly, individuals accessing our Web sites are subject to monitoring. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage to this service are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under applicable federal law.

### Aggregated tracking information

We analyze visitors use of our sites by tracking information such as pageviews, traffic flow, search terms, and click through. We use this information to improve our sites. We do not share any information with third part companies that can identify an individual user.

We use a third party web analytics service to improve our web site performance and user experience. We use this information to improve usability on our sites and to help support our customers online needs. The tracking system does not reveal any personally identifiable information, such as names or email address.

### Contact Information

www.interactivebrands.com welcomes your comments regarding this Privacy Policy. If you have any questions regarding our Privacy Policy, or this Web site, please contact us.
